Let me introduce myself first.
Hello everyone, I am Jimmy from MarvelousDiana.
Today I will show you how to make a few types of sleeves.
First of all, I will introduce the first type of sleeve, a lantern sleeve.
When I make this type of sleeve, because this type of sleeve is a relatively long sleeve,
I will first adjust the length of the sleeve to make it longer overall.
Then here I will use an interlock to set an interlock.
Cut it off as a sleeve.
Here I only cut the sleeve out first.
After straightening it, I will shrink the sleeve a little bit.
Let the pleats overlap at the sleeve position.
Then here I will use 100% elasticity for the sleeve.
Adjust its proportion to 100.
It can help us maintain the original length of this line very well,
so that it is not easy to be stretched.
If there are any questions later, I will answer them in the Q&A section.
This is an automatic fitting.
Are you talking about fitting clothes or fitting virtual models?
Then here,
because I need more pleats here,
I will first use the extension tool to add some fabric to the sleeve.
But before using the extension tool,
I want to determine where the center of the sleeve is.
So I added a straight line at the center of the sleeve.
We can also add straight lines in several different ways.
For example,
adjust the width of the sleeve by an average section or press the 100% section.
Then here I will switch to the extension tool.
When we use the extension tool,
click on one side of the sleeve.
We click on the other side,
and then click on the middle line of the extension.
We can extend from the middle to both sides.
To avoid the effect of the sleeve in clothes,
We need to freeze it first
Then we can see some creases
Then here, after I use the
I think the creases of the clothing
I still want to extend it a little bit, so that it has more fabric
This one has a live broadcast. The live broadcast will be uploaded next week.
Here we try to make sure that the length of the sleeve and the sleeve is the same
So here I adjusted their length
Try to keep their difference not very big
Then here I give the virtual model a change of a position
After changing the position, I will give my sleeve versions
Use the pressure
We open the triangle next to the pressure
You can see on this side
We can set the pressure value for the second and second seat of the small number
We just need a slight sense of fluttering
So we can make the pressure value smaller
Let it have a little bit of a sense of holding
And then this one, this one, uh, after the process is over, I'm going to reduce the resolution and then I'm going to simulate it so that it's more smooth
This is the first one that the lantern embroidered and then we come to the second one
These embroideries are all some of the more basic embroidery and there will be a few more blue ones
And then the second one is the road shoulder embroidery
If you want to make a road shoulder embroidery, you first need to make a loop line in the position of the mountain and then you need to make a
A longer one
A board so I set the line and then I cut the long board out
And then we delete the shoulder board and show the shoulder of the model
On this side, I'm going to freeze the long board and then I'm going to avoid it when we're adjusting the sleeve board
Uh, let him have some unstable situations
And then I'm going to use the extension tool to extend the board so that it has more fabric
So that we have more wrinkles on the sleeves
If you think this curve is not smooth, you can adjust it yourself
Uh, and here I'm going to stretch the board a little bit to make it have more fabric
I
And then here I try to make his sleeves
Uh, this one
The corner of the corner is a straight corner so that when we sew it up there will be a protruding protruding place
And now I'm going to activate this one. It's a relatively thin board
After activating this board, I'm going to apply 100 of the elastic ratio to it
So that it can maintain the original length of the line
Is not stretched
A larger chart this this
Bigger mouse chart
That's just because it's a pre-recorded video so there's no way to zoom in on the mouse
It's going to be this one and then I'm going to put it in the video I made and then I'm going to upload the one that I haven't speed up
You can go to our Bilibili website and watch our video.
The phone is a little small, you can change to a computer next time.
If your computer is full screen, you should be able to see it clearly.
Then here I will reduce its particle diameter.
Let it have more wrinkles
But in fact, in addition to reducing the particle diameter, we can also use the selection grid tool.
We use the selection grid tool.
After selecting the grid, we click on the right button.
Here we can see a division.
The division here is the same as the division in other software.
After you click on the division, it will automatically double the division according to your grid.
Then we check.
Let's check the grid.
You can see that the grid will be more dense in this place.
After that, if you have more details in your clothing, you can also use this method.
Make it a little bit more detailed.
Then here we can see that it has some wrinkles.
There is some stretch in this place.
Then if we want to solve this stretch in this place, we need to make this long strip longer.
Because its stretch is because this long strip is too short and a little tight.
So it caused some pull.
After we make it a little longer, we can solve this problem.
Then here I want this sleeve part to be a little bit harder.
So I applied a grid to it.
And it adds a little bit of its gold finish.
And it has the strength of the curve.
It makes it a little bit harder.
So it's a little bit more flat.
Okay.
Next time I'll try to enlarge the mouse a little bit.
And then here I have the third sleeve.
The third sleeve is the closing sleeve.
We need to make a lot of folds on the sleeve.
So here we need the sleeve to be long enough.
So that it has enough fabric to make some folds.
And then here I set up some lines.
And then I made a vertical line based on the curve.
After we cut the seam.
We select all the lines.
All the lines will be aligned to the outside of the panel.
And add points.
Then we have a lot of straight lines on our panel.
After we save the other side of the panel.
We can see that the current panel's connection is canceled.
So we can choose it.
If it's symmetrical.
The two sides are of the same information.
We can give it a symmetrical panel.
Set up a symmetrical panel.
We can edit one side at a time.
The other side will also be edited at the same time.
I added a straight line here.
The main reason is because I want to have equal lines.
Extend this panel a little bit.
So that the number of extensions is the same every time.
When we extend, click the right-click.
You can enter the number of extensions in the panel.
You can see the number of extensions in the panel.
Then here we can see.
After we extend.
There are some deformations in the 3D window.
We need to rearrange it.
When arranging.
Try not to make a difference with the model's arm.
Then here I will delete some.
Not too smooth lines.
I will adjust the curve line better.
After the adjustment is complete.
We select the top of this panel line.
Then we set the elasticity.
After we set the elasticity.
You can see that there are some folds now.
But it doesn't feel enough yet.
I want you to draw more.
At this time it will decrease.
It will decrease its elasticity ratio.
Let it draw more folds.
At the same time.
This one below.
This panel line below.
I also reduced its elasticity ratio.
Let it draw some folds at the same time.
Here.
I just want to make it.
The position of the sleeve.
There are more folds.
So I'm going to pull the sleeve up a little bit.
You can see that this place will also have folds.
Folding points.
Then.
After the production is completed.
I will select the panel on this side.
First solve the joint.
Then align.
If your panel.
It was originally linked.
You can't do it.
You can't directly align it to the other side.
Then the third sleeve.
The draw sleeve.
It's done.
It's all simple and basic.
This is the fourth sleeve.
A non-sew.
When making non-sew.
We only need to draw a rectangular panel.
So I put the original panel.
The sleeve panel.
30 seconds.
We will add a long strip.
After the rectangular panel.
We sew it together.
In the original sleeve.
The position of the sleeve.
Then here.
I need to adjust the shape of this panel.
Make it look more natural.
So.
In order to.
Make the two sides.
Adjust.
More symmetrical.
I'm in it.
I added a straight line in the context of its sleeve.
Then I will weak the bottom of the sleeve.
Pull it up.
To make the bottom shorter.
Then the top is longer.
Then adjust the curve of the sleeve.
On this side, I want to make this non-sew have more wrinkles, so I will make it a little longer.
On this side, I chose the line of the sleeve.
I applied 100 of the elasticity to avoid the sleeve being too long.
Then I stretched it.
Then I need to reduce some particle diameter here to see how the details are now.
I think there are still too many faces at the bottom, so I still shrink it a little bit.
OK.
Then I try to adjust the curve a little bit.
So that the sleeve has a nice curve.
If you want more wrinkles, you can make it stronger.
OK.
After the first side is finished, we just continue to align it to the other side.
Then this simple non-sew is finished.
On this side, I lowered the particle diameter.
Then the next sleeve.
This sleeve is the gourd sleeve.
When making this sleeve, it will be relatively long overall.
Then I first set a few.
According to the flat surface line curve.
According to the curve of the inner line.
Then after setting three inner lines.
I will draw a horizontal inner line.
After choosing those long lines, I will cut it off and divide it into several parts.
Then I will separate it.
On their flat surface line.
I will add one point.
But they are separated up and down.
Then here I choose the bottom of the flat surface line curve.
Set the hexagonal diameter.
The same is to add a few points.
The point of addition is mainly to let me adjust the flat surface later.
I will adjust it more conveniently.
Then after adjustment.
I will turn it into a curve line.
Then I choose the straight line point on the same side.
I will unify it to the left.
Then let it expand.
Then choose the other side to the right.
Form a shape similar to a gourd.
Then select all the lines.
Turn it into a curve line.
This side has not been turned yet.
Then I first simulated it.
See how it works now.
Then turn it into a curve line point.
You can see that the outline is strange now.
So I have to adjust the shape of this curve.
Make it more natural.
Today's live broadcast will have a video.
It will be broadcast next week.
Try to make this curve line transition more natural.
The effect will be better.
Then we can see that the seam will be larger now.
That is, after we select this flat surface.
We can right-click.
Then there is a change in the right-click menu.
We can change from the middle to both sides.
We just need to enter.
We just need to enter the number we want.
After the whole is shortened.
You can see that the sleeve is now wrapped around the model's arm.
Then here I give it a sleeve.
The sleeve of the sleeve.
I will sew this gourd on this sleeve.
Then here we use the free sewing tool.
When sewing.
Before pressing Shift.
Can sew on multiple sheets.
Then here.
We can see that the effect is not very natural now.
So here I delete the original sewing line.
Then the top and bottom.
The upper and lower sewing lines are separated.
Just sew from the bottom.
Sew from the top.
Then I will adjust the folding angle of the bottom sewing line separately.
Let it fold outward.
There are some.
The gourd will be more.
Harder.
Some.
Then after the manufacturing was done.
I will match to the wrong side.
Well.
This is a simple gourd line.
Placing online.
All right, the next is another piece of windER.
Honestly.
This embroider.
the bottom plate of the model will be very wide and very large.
Here I first draw a inner line,
but it does not extend to the position of the sleeve 3.
Then I use the internal multidirectional tool.
When drawing the inner line,
I press the Ctrl key to add a curve point.
Then when I draw the end point,
I click the right mouse button
to set the axis of the mirror in the spring.
Open the mirror,
we can modify the axis.
Then here I will separate the top and bottom two plates,
and cut it into pieces.
After we delete one side,
we concentrate on making one side,
and then after making it,
we will match it to the other side.
Then here I use the extension tool,
extend the bottom plate of this plate,
so that the bottom plate is wider.
Then here I use the extension tool,
extend the bottom plate of this plate,
so that the bottom plate is wider.
Then next I will give it a harder leather material from the outside.
I give it a leather material first,
mainly because I want it to hold up the whole thing,
so that it is smoother.
Then here I give it an external model.
I will convert it into a negative model.
After we insert the negative model,
there is no conflict between the negative model and the plate.
In NMD11,
we added a negative model with a conflict effect,
so we select the negative model,
and open the conflict.
The material will have conflicts with the negative model.
Then at this time,
we need to rearrange this plate,
so that it does not conflict with the negative model.
After we have arranged it, we can see that the problem can be avoided.
Then, because I think this sleeve is not wide enough, so I still use the extension tool to expand it.
Then here I will apply a slightly softer wool fabric to it.
So that it can have some folds, but now the folds are not natural enough.
That is to say, I will give it a fold angle according to the curve line.
After saving some grain lines, I will give it a fold angle.
OK.
After applying the fold angle, you can see that our board has an obvious fold effect.
The effect will be more obvious after hardening.
But the fold of the top board is not very natural.
So now we have to adjust the fold of the top board.
Because the board on this side is wider, I will make it narrower.
OK.
Similarly, I will make the bottom of the board narrower.
So that it can be as close as possible to the model's arm.
And the bottom will be wider.
OK.
Then here, due to the effect of the folding angle I just set, it disappeared, so I need to add it again here.
After we hard it, let it fold up first, and then finish the hardening, delete the inner line, and then we will process it to make the effect more natural.
After finishing one side, we will align it to the other side.
If you are making some relatively wide models, you can't hold it up.
At this time, you need to import a model from the outside, so that this model can support your fabric or clothing.
Thank you for watching.
This is the effect of a lala sleeve.
Then continue to make the next sleeve.
This kind of sleeve is called the electric shoulder sleeve.
I will put the shoulder up a little bit.
So here I set the inner line first.
Based on the curve, the inner line is created.
We can also adjust the shoulder of the inner line.
Then here I made a horizontal line of the inner line.
After that, I will fold it up and down.
Then here I will use the extension tool directly.
We click on the inner line, and we can also extend this line.
After we select the inner line.
Then we can directly extend it.
Here I try to control the extension.
The number of extensions is the same.
Let the length of the upper and lower two panels be almost the same.
You can see that the shoulder of the shoulder is not stopped yet.
So I will give it a harder fabric.
Let it stop a little bit.
If the effect is not enough.
We can increase its bending strength a little bit.
Let it become harder overall.
But now because the curve of the curve line is not very good.
That is to say, look at its sleeves.
It's a little bumpy.
So I need to adjust its curve.
Make the curve line a little more natural.
If you want to make the sleeves harder.
You can adjust the curve of the upper and lower two panels up and down.
Adjust it.
Let it have one.
There will be an obvious angle in the three-dimensional window.
Its hardening effect is done like this.
Then we can actually give this.
The plate of the shoulder of the shoulder.
A harder fabric.
Make it harder.
Then the plate below.
Give it a softer surface.
In addition to adjusting the plate here.
We can also adjust the folding angle of the sewing line.
Make the folding effect of this place more obvious.
Make the angle more obvious.
This is how to make the shoulder of the shoulder of the shoulder.
All are some relatively simple sleeves.
Then the next is the next sleeve.
I will make a calf sleeve here.
When making a calf sleeve.
I will raise its sleeve height overall.
Make its sleeve height a little higher.
After raising its sleeve height.
There will be enough fabric to make some folds.
Then.
Here.
I will set a vertical sleeve line according to the curve.
I will do the same.
When making a sleeve line.
Click the right button.
You can create a straight sleeve line.
In this way.
This is another step.
Let's make a draft for our fabric.
Here we use the seam to cut from the side of the fabric.
Let's set some shapes.
Make it aligned with the outside of the fabric.
Then.
Cut off the two pieces on the left.
Here.
I used a symmetrical sleeve.
But now.
There is a symmetrical relationship with the sleeve.
And the seam is symmetrical.
So.
In this case, I need to uninstall the link first and then set it to match the board separately.
The board set in this way can be matched to the editor, but its support line is not matched.
Then here I will use the extension tool to extend this leg sleeve to the outside.
Make it extend and have more fabric to make some folds.
After the extension is completed, I will delete all the rib threads first.
Then adjust these obvious corners to make the curve of this place more natural.
After the adjustment is completed, we need to sew the board and arrange the operation.
Here we need to first join the opposite board with the back of the sleeve.
Here we are.
We need to sew the top part first before simulating.
As you can see, in the shoulder of the table, we have a large amount of fabric.
But there is no support, so it can't be supported.
Then to make it have more fabric, I will make the embroidered line.
Let's go up a little bit
Here I will give this panel line to apply elasticity
But when using elasticity
I added a straight line here
Because I want to go on this line
The elasticity of this line is separated
We can reduce the proportion of the elasticity a little bit
So it can draw a lot of people
And then here
After I activate all the panels
I will change the model knowledge
After changing the knowledge
I will import a model made from the outside
It is also imported in the form of a copy
After the copy is imported
We
Need to open the conflict of this copy
If you are using the previous version of MD11
Your copy has no conflict effect
If you want to make the model you import have a conflict effect
You need to import it into the model form
You can see that there is no conflict in our copy now
We need to open its conflict
After opening, you can see that our stack of folds is affected by this copy
Let it hold up
Then I will lower the number of this elasticity a little bit more
Let it have more folds
And at the bottom of this place
I will also apply elasticity to it
Make some folds effect
This is the process of making the leg
And then I will lower its particle diameter
Let it have more details
This will have a recording process
The recording will usually be uploaded in the next week
And then I will push it to the other side after I have finished the connection of the version
This is a simple way to make a leg embroidery
And then here I will introduce two types of sewing methods
I will introduce two types of sewing methods
First one is the frame tells
The first one is simpler
And the second one will be more complicated
Now this thing I will introduce is the simpler one
I will lengthen this board as a whole, and when we lengthen it, we only lengthen it horizontally, so we need to press the Shift key, or you need to open the lock in the spring, so that we can adjust its width and height separately.
We need to adjust it to be three times the length of the original board, so we need to set 300% here, and then I will generate the internal line based on the curve line here.
The number of internal lines here is calculated like this.
If its internal line number is 3, n-1 square, so if I need to make 27,
then I need to set it to 26.
Then here I will use the fold line tool to give it the internal line and use some fold angles.
Then we need to make a fold with three internal lines.
Here I need to delete the original fold line first, and then simulate it.
After we harden it, its folding effect will be more obvious.
Then we use the fold angle tool to fold it up.
Here we also need to know that if you use this tool to fold, it will not be like this, but it will be directly to the point below.
That is because you may not align the internal lines of the board to the external lines of the board, and add a straight line.
Because when it is folded, it is identified by the straight line point.
We can see that now this part of the sleeve, this fold, is a little bit crooked.
We can see that this part of the sleeve is a little bit crooked.
So we need to check this fold line first.
We can see that this fold line, because I am three times longer overall,
So we can see that this fold line, because I am three times longer overall,
So that the distance of each internal line is the same as that of the fold line.
So the sleeve of this board will not be stretched.
After we select this fold line, we reverse activate the fold line.
Then you can see that the movement of this place will be smoother
Because the lines of each red line are very long
That is, there will be no sagging
Then we finish the side
And then we do the other side
This is a relatively simple fold
There will be a screen later
So if you didn't see it in the front
You can go to our e-zeng official website next week to see the screen
This is the first relatively simple fold embroidery
Then the second one will be more difficult
On this side
I need to draw a internal shape on the board first
Then I draw this range
Is the range I need to make the fold
Then I choose the internal line of these two legs
I will follow the curve
The internal line of the body
If you want a few folds here
You set the number of its internal lines as the number of the fold you want
minus one
For example, I want to fold seven
So here I need to set six internal lines in it
Then after the drawing is finished
I will copy it and edit this piece of paper separately
Then I will cut this piece of paper
Only keep this part of the internal shape I set
And then I will take this piece with the internal line of these boards
The same is three times the length
After three times the length
In fact, it is only three times the length of the board above
So we are the same as the three of us
Three internal lines as one fold
One is the top and the bottom
Is the third times the number of the top and the bottom
Then here I set two internal lines between each internal line
But this one we can pay attention to this one
I'm going to cut this one
Cut this one
But this one
We can notice that this one
I'm the only one who didn't make it three times longer
It's because this piece of paper is in this position
We need to make sure it's the same length as it used to be
Suddenly we need to set the folding angle for him here
We use the flip-folding tool to give him a folding angle
As you can see
If I simulate it now
The board will fall down
So I need to balance the gravity of the scene
Use it to simulate when there is no gravity
So when we simulate
He can fold it up more easily and simply
And then here
I'm going to make this board longer and taller
After we select the other sleeves
Here
I will take the curve of the position of this sleeve
I'm going to take the curve of this sleeve
I'm going to take it to the top of this piece of board that I created
So here I need to make the whole of his sleeve
So after I select all the internal lines on this board
I'm going to align it to the outside of the board and add a dot
You can see that now every line is the same as the outside of the board
See every line is different
Then how do I pull the
I'm going to use the folding tool to make him the inside line
After the layout of the inside
We directly place it in the position that is originally appropriate
You can observe the inside line position in the three-dimensional window
What about that kind of thing
We fold it in this position.
So the next inner line needs to be extended from here.
So I need to draw a horizontal inner line here.
Let it extend all the way to this position.
Then continue to hook the outer line of the panel.
Hook it as an inner shape and place it on the panel below.
Then do the same operation.
After hooking a panel line, we will draw a horizontal inner line.
But this inner line needs to be extended to
the back two inner lines of the panel line.
After hooking the panel line,
if we look at the 3D window,
the shape of the panel line is the same as the original panel line.
If we sew it,
we use this panel line to sew the original panel line.
If we use this panel line to sew the original panel line,
there will be no stretch.
Here I select all the inner lines that I just hooked.
We will merge them together.
After merging, I will cut it off.
Then delete the unnecessary panel lines.
You can see that this curve now
can correspond to the curve of the original sleeve 3.
They are the same.
Then here you can notice that
there are some protruding places in this part.
Our current problem is to solve this protruding place.
We need to delete this protruding place.
Let this place be smoother.
But how do we make it here?
Here I will use the same hook tool.
After selecting this panel line,
we hook it to the panel line.
Then when we hook it,
we press Ctrl R to paste it.
The panel line can be automatically pasted.
Then we can see that this panel line
will have an intersection with this vertical panel line.
After adding a point to the intersection,
we delete this part.
We can see that this part of the panel line
is the part of the panel line.
Then we look at the 3D window.
This part of the panel line
can actually be sewn with this part of the panel line.
So that they can produce a folding effect.
Just like making a foldable dress.
This place needs to be folded.
Then we need to put the corresponding panel line
on the other side.
After we paste it to the other side,
we will cut it off again.
You can see that this place
will get a smoother transition.
We can see this transition
in the 3D window.
Then,
we use the same method
to cut off all the protruding parts.
I first made a side of the panel line.
Then we cut it off.
After we have selected these panel lines,
we glue them together
to this other side of the 3D panel line.
We use this panel line as a foundation
to face it to each other.
And then,
I will select the inner line here and delete the rest of the place.
This place can't be deleted.
The main reason is that the inner line of this place may have some crossings and so on.
There is no way to cut it directly.
We need to merge it and then cut it.
Now we can observe that the shape of the 3D window of this board is actually the same as the original board.
We can directly sew this board in the place of their sleeve and there will be no pull.
Then
Here we need to do something.
We need to sew up these folds first.
Here I sewed it alone.
I want to explain to you why this place needs to be folded like this.
We can observe the movement of this sewing line in the 3D window.
You can see that the sewing lines in the 3D window are not crossed.
When we sew, we also sew from the middle to both sides.
You can see that this is the direction of the sewing line.
We can minimize the tasted Reinaben as it is in reality.
While arriving to the 3D board, we can heat up this
board outside and
Then I immediately used a lining sewing tool.
Sew these go directly on it.
When we sew, if you don't know what's going on, you
can just do it in 3D.
Observing and sewing.
Just ensure that the sewing lines in the 3D window are not crossed.
Then when sewing is complete.
After setting the peak, the place to copy will be more even.
You can see that half of the embroidery is finished.
After the work is finished, we paste it in a symmetrical version.
Then copy them.
I move this piece of board to the position of the arm of the model.
Because we can't use the arranging point directly.
If we use the arranging point directly, we need to redo the previous sewing effects.
So we can only move this piece of board through the positioning ball.
Then I use the free movement here.
I also want to introduce the sewing tool.
When we sew this kind of fold, we need to jump over the place that has already been sewn.
We can see that we jump from this place to this place that has already been sewn.
Then we continue to sew directly from this place.
We can observe the position of the sewing line in the 3D window.
To avoid some mistakes after sewing.
After the front panel is finished, we continue to sew the back panel in the same way.
Then sew the hem of the sleeve to the bottom.
So we sew the hem of the sleeve to the top弼
So it goes straight.
Sew both edges of the sleeve, which alsoải
So whether or not it's going to be wrong.
We finish sewing the shape and thickness
운동
Monaten
Mrs
j
I говорят
let it place
It looks natural.
This fold is a bit easier than the previous one, and it's a little softer.
And after we make another anymore, we just align it on the other side.
Does it crack?
Is it cracked?
Everyone
Am I cracked?
Let's see if there is any problem.
If you have any questions, I will answer your questions after I finish the explanation.
If you have any questions, please ask me.
This is how to make the second folding sleeve.
After we finish the explanation, I will merge the panels into one panel.
Then we can open the high quality line and see what the effect of this folding is like.
OK
Next is the last way to make the sleeve.
This is a little bit complicated.
Because it has many layers.
So I will explain it slowly.
First, I stretch the sleeve.
Then I use a 3D drawing tool.
After I draw a line on the sleeve,
I can clearly locate the position of this line on the panel.
Then I convert it into an internal shape.
After converting it into an internal shape, we can see that this curve is not very smooth.
We can make it a little bit rounder.
After that, we continue to draw the second line.
I will make it a shape similar to a fish scale.
After that, we take a fish scale and make it a 3D shape.
This fish scale will have a overlap effect.
You can imagine what fish scales are like.
Should be one layer after one layer.
After the first group is finished, I will directly copy and paste it.
Make the second group.
Then at this position, I need some super glue for it.
In this position, I need to make some adjustments to some of the out-of-the-frame layers and some of the out-of-the-frame layers that are not aligned with each other.
You can see that there are some effects that are similar to the one in Yuning.
Then here I set the layer border, and then I will make a border for it.
The position of this layer border that I set is the position that will be pulled out when the layers are aligned.
Similarly, on the other side, I will align these layer borders to the out-of-the-frame layer first.
Then align it to the layer border on this side.
Then here I will also set the layer border for the other side, but it also has a wrapper effect.
Then we need to align this layer border to the top of this layer border.
The top one doesn't look like it, but because I adjusted the position of this point here, so we need to adjust it again here.
Let it align this root and this root of the inner line.
But after adjustment, we have to adjust it again here to adjust it.
Because when we align the inner line to the inner line, it will automatically recognize the inner line closest to it.
So we need to move it as close as possible to the inner line we want.
Then let it align
Then we have a cross effect.
Then here, I also made one more to the bottom of this position.
Then, after the inner line is finished, we will start to make its shape.
After the interior line and the outside of the board are formed into a closed shape, we can hook the board.
After hooking it into a board, we can see that the position of the hook will actually be based on the position of the board in the 2D window to be created.
But if we want to extract the board from its original position,
the simplest way is to copy this board and paste it.
We put it on the outside.
The cloned board will automatically be outside or inside the original board based on the selected option.
After writing the connection,
I will
cut off this board and keep the part I want.
Here I first keep the position of this sleeve 3,
and then continue to clone to the outside.
After writing the connection board,
we select this loop line and this one,
because I just want to keep this shape.
Then you can see that
in fact,
the board that has been extracted can be re-printed back to the original board shape.
The place where we overlap will be the place where the layer relationship will appear afterwards.
Then continue to clone.
Here we need to solve the connection of the cloned board.
The main reason is that if you do not solve the connection of the connection,
the board above and the board below are connected.
When you edit its internal shape and cut,
it will operate simultaneously.
Then you can see that
every piece of board we extract is able to be re-printed on the original board.
Now I have been extracting the internal shape I want,
and I have to copy this one.
I have to copy this one.
Then I will save this one.
I will save this one.
If the internal shape I want,
you can copy it.
Another point is,
if the internal shape you extract is above the original shape you want,
this one,
but your internal shape is older,
If it is more than half, it may cause some errors when you cut it off.
Then you can see that now we can make it into the original file.
But it actually has a lot of overlap.
We need to show the effect of this overlap.
First of all, I'm going to sew up the sleeve and the sleeve cage.
When we sew the sleeve, we can reactivate the unrelated version first, adjust it piece by piece.
We can delete some of the lines that I don't need.
I just did it.
I'm going to sew up some of the lines that I don't need when I cut it off.
And then here, I sewed up the first piece of sleeve 3.
I'm going to keep sewing it the other way around.
Sew it on the sleeve of the front piece.
You can see that there may be some errors in the position of the sewing.
We need this part to overlap with this part.
So I need to adjust the sewing line here again.
I'm going to stretch the sewing line of the front piece up a little bit and you can see that this part can overlap.
There's a layer relationship.
Then I'm going to sew it up.
But for better sewing results, I'm going to delete this part.
After that, I will extend the sewing line to the front piece.
After extending the sewing line, we also need to extend the sewing line on the sleeve side.
Then you can see that we're fine.
It's a bit tight.
And this is where I'm going to close it.
We actually have this part on the inside of the outer plate
We need to sew this side on this inner line of it
Sew it up
After sewing it up
We need to sew up the side seam
We can observe from the bottom
How far is the seam of the car window
After sewing these two panels
We will use the same method to continue to make subsequent panels
You can see that when sewing
We see that the length of our sewing line should actually be in this position
But we need to stay at the end of this sewing line
Then
Continue to sew from this point
Because our layer ratio is this in the outer layer
Then this is the second layer
The third layer
Then after the sewing is over
I will first move the two panels on top that have been sewed up
And set its level
Let it simulate the outer layer
Then this side
This place is also a overlapping relationship
So we need to sew it up
To get it to have a closed effect
And then there's a slit
Here we need to sew up the lining
When sewing a window
We need to observe the location of the sewing line in a 3D window
Right?
Because if you do this matter of sewing here
It will actually have some stretching
Then here I activate this
After this cold version
After we adjust the results to zero
Let's simulate again
See if there is any unstable situation
And the situation of stretching
And then we will continue to sew this part without a seam
The seam is sewed up
When sewing
We can click on the 3D window panel
We can see that there will be a blue matching point on the 2D window panel
We can use this matching point to position the seam
And then sew it
This will not be easy to sew up the error
Then we will use the same method to continue sewing the fourth layer
The same
At the end of the last sewing line
We need to start sewing from this place
This is the fourth layer
We need to start sewing at the third layer of this panel
If there is a gap
We can use the edit network tool
Select the network tool to make a selection for the network
And adjust
Then we need to overlap the panel line and the web line
Sew them up
And then we will continue the way to sew this panel line
We will continue to sew on the longer end to the third layer
This sewing area must be long
If it's not long enough
This place is very likely to have some stretching
We can click on the panel and locate it
We need to sew and place
Then start sewing from the positioning position
Then continue to use the same method
Sew to the following panel line
The following versions will be sewed up one by one
This place just needs to be careful
Don't make any mistakes
That's it
You need to remember the level relationship
We still need to adjust it after we use it
Because if you keep the level relationship open
In the subsequent simulation process
There may be conflicts with some unrelated versions
And then cause some unstable situations
And then?
Here we have the last piece of paper left
Then we sew this piece of paper up
The same way
Sew it up
At the very top
At the very bottom
And then after sewing
I'll give you all the levels
And then the outer layer
Now it's already at the very bottom
So I'm going to set the level relationship to negative one
Let it be simulated to the very bottom
Then let it go all the way down
And then you have the whole line
And then you have to put it up
And then the inner hole
After the inner hole is ready
Then we sew it together
And then we do the other side
And then we have to sew the other side
Do the design
This is the same
Then the outer edge is sewn together
Again, this is pointed
But here we can do it in a whole line
Then we sew the side loops together
And row the inside line
This is also a seam prepared
Then we can see that there is a sharp point here.
I can use the round-shape curve tool to make a round corner.
This is a method of making multi-layer embroidery with more layers.
Remember to adjust the level of the layer after the work is finished.
After the work is finished, we will align it to the other side.
You can see the effect of the embroidery.
This time, I mainly want to show you how to do this kind of work.
This time, I want to show you how to do this kind of work.
I want to show you how to create different embroidery thoughts and how to change the version.
This is the multi-layer effect.
You can use it on clothes.
It also makes some multi-layer effects.
The design of the external model as a support.
It can make you make dresses.
You can make dresses.
Then you can hide the model
Then I find the one in the external model as a support
In that case, you can have some dresses
You can see that some dresses are some dresses with support
You can import the model from the external model
Then as a support, let it hold up the whole thing
This will have a video
The video will be uploaded next week
Do you have any questions now?
If you have any questions, you can now ask in the chat
I will answer you now
If there are some questions that are not clear
You can also add our official Koko technology support group
This group
The group number is at the bottom left corner of this screen
Then enter the group's password is HANA
You can add more groups
After entering the group
We can answer your questions in that group
Answer your questions about using software